AV
New York University Archives
Audiovisual Collection
1956-2011
AV
New York University Archives
5032.0 items
- Audiovisual Recordings
  - Bedford-Stuyvesant Clinics, Part 2, 1962 March 13; AV83; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.). (Box 2, Reel 83)
    Content Note
    This recording appears to be part two of the recording "Urban League Presents: Bedford-Stuyvesant Looks to Psychiatric Needs" on AV523. It is unclear whether this recording ever aired on WNYU.
    Related Material
    This tape is related to materials in RG 39.5, Records of WNYU (Radio Station: New York, N.Y.).
    Technical Access
    1/4" open reel original; Scotch Magnetic Tape (3M).
  - Italian Centennial, Tape I, 1961 April 17; AV97
    Ortona, Egidio, 1910-1996; Pollock, Thomas Clark, 1902-; Stoddard, George Dinsmore, 1897-1981
  - Italian Centennial, Tape II, 1961 April 17; AV98 (Box 2, Reel 98)
    Salomone, A. William, (Arcangelo William), 1915-1989
  - Italian Centennial, Tape III, 1961 April 17; AV99 (Box 2, Reel 99)
  - Speech by John F. Kennedy, 1960; AV113 (Box 2, Reel 113)
  - Viewpoint International: Refugees from Behind the Iron Curtain, 1956; AV425 (Box 10, Reel 425)
  - Pipes and Pedals of New York, 1962 August 6; AV115; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.). (Box 3, Reel 115)
    This recording concerns the history of organ instruments. It was created by the Documentary Unit of the Communications Arts Group and broadcasted on WNYU. The host was Walt Michaels and the organist player featured on the recording is Dick Wolitoch.
    1/4" open reel original; 28:38 min; 7 1/2 speed; Scotch Magnetic Tape (3M).
    New York University. Communication Arts Group.
  - Speech at School of Law, 1960; AV161; Nixon, Richard M., (Richard Milhous), 1913-1994 (Box 4, Reel 161)
  - Viewpoint International: Puerto Rico as by American Students, 1956; AV422 (Box 10, Reel 422)
  - Campus Editorial: Is Chivalry Dead?, 1956; AV423 (Box 10, Reel 423)
  - Campus Editorial: Freedom of Speech/Viewpoint International: Christmas in Your Country, 1956; AV424 (Box 10, Reel 424)
  - Campus Editorial: Has the U.S. Fulfilled Its Role in the Hungarian Revolt/Viewpoint International: The French Drama, 1957; AV426 (Box 11, Reel 426)
  - Campus Editorial: Should Capital Punishment Be Abolished in the U.S./Viewpoint International: The French Novel, 1957; AV427 (Box 11, Reel 427)
  - Campus Editorial: Are Athletics Being Overemphasized in Our Colleges and Universities/Viewpoint International: Italian Music, 1957; AV428 (Box 11, Reel 428)
  - Campus Editorial: Should American Policemen Carry Nightsticks Instead of Guns/Viewpoint International: Seminar in Western Europe, 1957; AV429 (Box 11, Reel 429)
  - Campus Editorial: What Will Be the Outcome of the Middle East Question/Viewpoint International: American Interests in Foreign Study, 1957; AV430 (Box 11, Reel 430)
  - Urban League Presents: Judge Delany, 1959; AV431 (Box 11, Reel 431)
  - Urban League Presents: Frank Turner, 1959; AV432 (Box 11, Reel 432)
  - Urban League Presents: A Lawyer Looks at Bigotry, 1959; AV433 (Box 11, Reel 433)
  - Urban League Presents: Organized Labor and Community Services (Part 1), 1959; AV434 (Box 11, Reel 434)
  - Urban League Presents: Organized Labor and Community Services (Part 2), 1959; AV435 (Box 11, Reel 435)
  - Urban League Presents: Do Our Hospitals Discriminate? (Part 1), 1959; AV436 (Box 11, Reel 436)
  - Urban League Presents: Do Our Hospitals Discriminate? (Part 2), 1959; AV437 (Box 11, Reel 437)
  - Urban League Presents: Educational Television, 1959; AV438 (Box 11, Reel 438)
  - Urban League Presents: Switchblade Knives, 1959; AV439 (Box 11, Reel 439)
  - Urban League Presents: Negro History in the School Curriculum, 1959; AV440 (Box 11, Reel 440)
  - Urban League Presents: Equal Opportunity 1959, AV441 (Box 11, Reel 441)
  - Urban League Presents: Negro Influence in American History, 1959; AV442 (Box 11, Reel 442)
  - Urban League Presents: Can Psychiatry Help Juvenile Offenders? (Part 1), 1959; AV443 (Box 11, Reel 443)
  - Urban League Presents: Can Psychiatry Help Juvenile Offenders? (Part 2), 1959; AV444 (Box 11, Reel 444)
  - Urban League Presents: Open Neighborhoods, 1959; AV445 (Box 11, Reel 445)
  - Urban League Presents: Opportunities in Teaching, 1960; AV446 (Box 11, Reel 446)
  - Urban League Presents: Organizing Minority Workers, 1960; AV447 (Box 11, Reel 447)
  - Urban League Presents: Problems of Slum Clearance, Part 1, 1960; AV448 (Box 11, Reel 448)
  - Urban League Presents: Integration in Public Housing, 1960; AV450 (Box 11, Reel 450)
  - Urban League Presents: Your Social Security, Part 1, 1960; AV451 (Box 11, Reel 451)
  - Urban League Presents: Your Social Security, Part 2, 1960; AV452 (Box 11, Reel 452)
  - Urban League Presents: Employment Discrimination in N.Y.C., 1960; AV453 (Box 11, Reel 453)
  - Urban League Presents: Shakespeare in Harlem, 1960; AV454 (Box 11, Reel 454)
  - Urban League Presents: The Need for Improving Minimum Wage Standards in N.Y.C., 1960; AV455 (Box 11, Reel 455)
  - Urban League Presents: You and Your Parents' Association, 1960; AV456 (Box 11, Reel 456)
  - Urban League Presents: Is There a Puerto Rican Problem?, 1959-1960; AV457 (Box 11, Reel 457)
  - Urban League Presents: Your Workman's Compensation, 1960; AV458 (Box 11, Reel 458)
  - Urban League Presents: You and Unemployment Insurance, 1960; AV459 (Box 11, Reel 459)
  - Urban League Presents: Protest, Part 1, 1960; AV460 (Box 11, Reel 460)
  - Urban League Presents: Protest, Part 2, 1960; AV461 (Box 11, Reel 461)
  - Urban League Presents: Let's Be Human, 1960; AV462 (Box 11, Reel 462)
  - Urban League Presents: The Negro Artist, Part 1, 1960; AV463 (Box 123, Reel 463)
  - Urban League Presents: The Negro Artist, Part 2, 1960; AV464 (Box 123, Reel 464)
  - Urban League Presents: Is There Discrimination in Auto Insurance?, 1960; AV465 (Box 123, Reel 465)
  - Urban League Presents: How to Organize a Rent Clinic, Part 1, 1960; AV466 (Box 123, Reel 466)
  - Urban League Presents: How to Organize a Rent Clinic, Part 2, 1960; AV467 (Box 11, Reel 467)
  - Urban League Presents: A Realtor Looks at Bigotry, 1960; AV468 (Box 123, Reel 468)
  - Urban League Presents: Homes for Homeless Children, Part 1, 1960; AV469 (Box 11, Reel 469)
  - Urban League Presents: Homes for Homeless Children, Part 2, 1960; AV470 (Box 12, Reel 470)
  - Urban League Presents: A Program for School Integration, Part 1, 1960; AV471 (Box 12, Reel 471)
  - Urban League Presents: Luxury Housing and Tenant Evictions, Part 1, 1961; AV472 (Box 12, Reel 472)
  - Urban League Presents: Luxury Housing and Tenant Evictions, Part 2, 1961 February 12; AV473; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.). (Box 12, Reel 473)
    1/4" open reel original; 14:23 min; Scotch Magnetic Tape (3M).
  - Urban League Presents: Be a Friend to a Boy, 1961 February 19; AV474; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.). (Box 12, Reel 474)
    1/4" open reel original; 14:29 min.
  - Urban League Presents: Cancer Prevention, 1961 February 26; AV475; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.). (Box 12, Reel 475)
    1/4" open reel original; 14:30 min; Scotch Magnetic Tape (3M).
  - Urban League Presents: The American Negro Looks at Africa, 1961 March 5; AV476; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.). (Box 12, Reel 476)
    1/4" open reel original; 14:26 min; Scotch Magnetic Tape (3M).
  - Urban League Presents: The Sharkey Brown Isaacs Law Effective, 1961 March 12; AV477; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.). (Box 12, Reel 477)
    1/4" open reel original; 13:58 min; Scotch Magnetic Tape (3M).
  - Urban League Presents: The Press and the Community, 1961 March 19; AV478; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.). (Box 12, Reel 478)
    1/4" open reel original; 13:36 min; Scotch Magnetic Tape (3M).
  - Urban League Presents: Call Me By My Rightful Name, 1961 March 26; AV479; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.). (Box 12, Reel 479)
    1/4" open reel original; 14:30 min.
  - Urban League Presents: Hardship Rent Increases, 1961; AV480; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.). (Box 12, Reel 480)
  - Urban League Presents: Building Private Interracial Housing, 1961 April 9; AV481; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.). (Box 12, Reel 481)
    1/4" open reel original; 14:24 min; Scotch Magnetic Tape (3M).
  - Urban League Presents: Do Negro G.I.'s Become Second-Class Veterans, Part 1, 1961 April 16; AV482; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.). (Box 12, Reel 482)
    1/4" open reel original; 14:34 min; Scotch Magnetic Tape (3M).
  - Urban League Presents: Do Negro G.I.'s Become Second-Class Veterans?, Part 2, 1961 April 23; AV483; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.). (Box 12, Reel 483)
  - Urban League Presents: Teenage Gangs, 1961 July 30; AV484; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.). (Box 12, Reel 484)
    1/4" open reel original; 14:27 min.
  - Urban League Presents: Community Hospitals in New York City, 1961 August 6; AV485; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.). (Box 12, Reel 485)
  - Urban League Presents: Conquest of Tensions, Part 1, 1961 August 13; AV486; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.). (Box 12, Reel 486)
  - Urban League Presents: Conquest of Tensions, Part 2, 1961 August 20; AV487; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.). (Box 12, Reel 487)
    1/4" open reel original; 14:32 min.
  - Urban League Presents: Stay in School, 1961 August 27; AV488; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.). (Box 12, Reel 488)
  - Urban League Presents: The Future of Labor Management Relations, 1961 September 3; AV489; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.). (Box 12, Reel 489)
    1/4" open reel original; 14:37 min.
  - Urban League Presents: How to Spot a Bigot, 1961 September 10; AV490; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.). (Box 12, Reel 490)
  - Urban League Presents: Should City Employees Join Unions?, 1961 September 17; AV491; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.). (Box 12, Reel 491)
  - Urban League Presents: The Reluctant African, 1961 September 24; AV492; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.). (Box 12, Reel 492)
    1/4" open reel original; 13:45 min.
  - Urban League Presents: Employing the Handicapped Worker, 1961 October 1; AV493; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.). (Box 12, Reel 493)
    1/4" open reel original; 13:32 min.
  - Urban League Presents: Townsend Harris and Free Education, 1961 October 9; AV494; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.). (Box 12, Reel 494)
    1/4" open reel original; 14:24 min.
  - Urban League Presents: Housing Violations, 1961 October 16; AV495; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.). (Box 12, Reel 495)
  - Urban League Presents: How to Look for a Job, 1961 October 23; AV496; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.). (Box 12, Reel 496)
    1/4" open reel original; 14:17 min.
  - Urban League Presents: Does Language Hamper Racial Understanding?, 1961 October 30; AV497; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.). (Box 12, Reel 497)
    Scope and Contents
    Original container has "WWRL" handwritten on the label. This recording may have also been broadcasted on WWRL, a radio station located in New York City.
  - Urban League Presents: Are Present School Boycotts the Answer?, 1961 November 6; AV498; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.). (Box 12, Reel 498)
    1/4" open reel original; 14:19 min.
  - Urban League Presents: Inside Angola, 1961 November 26; AV499; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.). (Box 12, Reel 499)
    1/4" open reel original; 14:39 min.
  - Urban League Presents: The Disgrace of New York's Migrant Labor, 1961 December 3; AV500; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.). (Box 12, Reel 500)
    1/4" open reel original; 14:16 min; Scotch Magnetic Tape (3M).
  - Urban League Presents: What Does Africa Really Want From Us?, Part I, 1961 December 10; AV501; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.). (Box 12, Reel 501)
    1/4" open reel original; 14:25 min.
  - Urban League Presents: What Does Africa Really Want From Us?, Part II, 1961 December 18; AV502; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.). (Box 12, Reel 502)
  - Urban League Presents: The Dilemma of the Negro Writer, part 1, 1961 December 25; AV503; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.). (Box 12, Reel 503)
  - Urban League Presents: The Dilemma of the Negro Writer, part 2, 1962 April 8; AV504; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.). (Box 12, Reel 504)
    1/4" open reel original; 14:10 min.
  - Urban League Presents: Echoes of Africa, 1962 April 16; AV505; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.). (Box 12, Reel 505)
    1/4" open reel original; 14:34 min.
  - Urban League Presents: Worker Exploitation, Part I, 1962 April 23; AV506; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.). (Box 12, Reel 506)
    1/4" open reel original; 14:18 min.
  - Urban League Presents: Worker Exploitation, Part II, 1962 April 29; AV507; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.). (Box 12, Reel 507)
  - Urban League Presents: Can Mayor's Contract Compliance Program Work?, part 1, 1962 May 7; AV508; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.). (Box 12, Reel 508)
  - Urban League Presents: Can Mayor's Contract Compliance Program Work?, Part 2, 1962 May 13; AV509; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.). (Box 123, Reel 509)
    1/4" open reel original; 15:10 min; Scotch Magnetic Tape (3M).
  - Urban League Presents: A Growing Crisis in the City's Welfare Program, 1962 May 20; AV510; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.). (Box 123, Reel 510)
    1/4" open reel original; 14:38 min; Scotch Magnetic Tape (3M).
  - Urban League Presents: Has Housing Integration Come to the Upper West Side?, 1962 May 28; AV511; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.). (Box 123, Reel 511)
  - Urban League Presents: What is AMSAC's Mission?, 1962 June 3; AV512; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.). (Box 123, Reel 512)
    1/4" open reel original; 13:08 min.
  - Urban League Presents: The Young Citizens, 1962 June 11; AV513; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.). (Box 13, Reel 513)
    1/4" open reel original; 14:44 min.
  - Urban League Presents: Your Rights When Arrested, 1962 June 24; AV514; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.). (Box 13, Reel 514)
    Original container has "WNJR" handwritten on the label. This recording may have also been broadcasted on WNJR, the college radio station for Washington and Jefferson College in Washington, Pennsylvania.
  - Urban League Presents: How to Land a Job in the Foreign Service, part 1, 1962 July 1; AV515; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.). (Box 13, Reel 515)
    1/4" open reel original; 14:23 min.
  - Urban League Presents: How to Land a Job in the Foreign Service, Part 2, 1962 July 9; AV516; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.). (Box 13, Reel 516)
    1/4" open reel original; 14:25 min; Scotch Magnetic Tape (3M).
  - Urban League Presents: The Blacks, 1962 July 16; AV517; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.). (Box 13, Reel 517)
    1/4" open reel original; 14:48 min; Scotch Magnetic Tape (3M).
  - Urban League Presents: Problems of Installment Buying ("Buying on Credit"), 1962 July 22; AV518; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.). (Box 13, Reel 518)
    1/4" open reel original; 14:36 min.
    This tape is related to materials in RG 39.5, Records of WNYU (Radio Station: New York, N.Y.).This tape is related to materials in RG 39.5, Records of WNYU (Radio Station: New York, N.Y.).
  - Urban League Presents: How to Apply for Public Housing, 1962 July 29; AV519; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.). (Box 13, Reel 519)
    1/4" open reel original; 14:22 min.
  - Urban League Presents: A Business with a Social Purpose, 1962 August 6; AV520; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.). (Box 13, Reel 520)
    1/4" open reel original; 14:46 min.
  - Urban League Presents: A Minute of Your Time, 1962 August 13; AV521; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.). (Box 13, Reel 521)
    1/4" open reel original; 14:28 min; Scotch Magnetic Tape (3M).
  - Urban League Presents: The Compulsive Drinker, 1962 August 19; AV522; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.). (Box 13, Reel 522)
  - Urban League Presents: Bedford-Stuyvesant Looks to Psychiatric Needs, 1962 August 27; AV523; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.). (Box 13, Reel 523)
    1/4" open reel original; 14:05 min.
  - Urban League Presents: Social Action in Education, 1962 September 3; AV524; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.). (Box 13, Reel 524)
    1/4" open reel original; 14:13 min; Scotch Magnetic Tape (3M).
  - Urban League Presents: Unmarried Mothers, 1962 September 9; AV525; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.). (Box 13, Reel 525)
    1/4" open reel original; 14:26 min.
  - Urban League Presents: A Report on School Dropouts, 1962 September 17; AV526; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.). (Box 13, Reel 526)
    1/4" open reel original; 14:55 min.
  - Urban League Presents: Is More Training the Answer to Better Social Service?, 1962 September 23; AV527; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.). (Box 13, Reel 527)
  - Urban League Presents: The Bible and Race Relations, Part 1, 1962 September 30; AV528; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.). (Box 13, Reel 528)
    1/4" open reel original; 13:04 min; Scotch Magnetic Tape (3M).
  - Urban League Presents: The Bible and Race Relations, Part 2, 1962 October 7; AV529; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.). (Box 13, Reel 529)
  - Urban League Presents: How Can School Dropouts Succeed?, part 1, 1962 October 14; AV530; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.). (Box 13, Reel 530)
  - Urban League Presents: How Can School Dropouts Succeed?, part 2, 1962 October 22; AV531; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.). (Box 13, Reel 531)
  - Urban League Presents: The Concluding Part of a Special Series on How Can the School Dropouts Succeed?, 1962 October 29; AV532; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.). (Box 13, Reel 532)
    1/4" open reel original; 14:16 min.
  - Urban League Presents: The Long Shadow of Little Rock, 1962 November 4; AV533; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.). (Box 13, Reel 533)
    1/4" open reel original; 14:17 min; Scotch Magnetic Tape (3M).
  - Urban League Presents: Haryou (A New Harlem Youth Project), 1962 November 18; AV534; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.). (Box 13, Reel 534)
    1/4" open reel original; 14:31 min; Scotch Magnetic Tape (3M).
  - Campus Editorial: Does the Current Trend in Popular Music Tend to Promote Juvenile Delinquency?, 1956; AV542 (Box 13, Reel 542)
  - Campus Editorial: Is the Quality of TV Programs Improving?, 1956; AV543 (Box 13, Reel 543)
  - Campus Editorial: Will We Have a Third World War?, 1956; AV544 (Box 13, Reel 544)
  - Viewpoint International: Religions in Russia, 1956; AV545 (Box 13, Reel 545)
  - Campus Editorial: Supreme Court Judicial Review, 1956; AV546 (Box 13, Reel 546)
  - Urban League Presents: A Program for School Integration, Part 3, 1960; AV548 (Box 13, Reel 548)
  - Urban League Presents: Parents in Public School Life, 1960; AV549 (Box 13, Reel 549)
  - Urban League Presents: Myths of Racial Discrimination, Part 1, 1960; AV550 (Box 13, Reel 550)
  - Urban League Presents: Myths of Racial Discrimination, Part 2, 1960; AV551 (Box 13, Reel 551)
  - Urban League Presents: Myths of Racial Discrimination, Part 3, 1960; AV552 (Box 13, Reel 552)
  - Urban League Presents: Myths of Racial Discrimination, Part 4, 1960; AV553 (Box 13, Reel 553)
  - Urban League Presents: The Death of Africa, 1960; AV554 (Box 14, Reel 554)
  - Urban League Presents: Democratic Program for Civil Rights, 1960; AV555 (Box 14, Reel 555)
  - Urban League Presents: A Republican Program for Civil Rights, 1960; AV556 (Box 14, Reel 556)
  - Urban League Presents: A Priest Looks at Harlem's Problems, Part 1, 1961 January 1; AV565; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.). (Box 14, Reel 565)
  - Urban League Presents: A Priest Looks at Harlem's Problems, Part 2, 1961 January 8; AV566; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.). (Box 14, Reel 566)
    1/4" open reel original; 14:12 min.
  - Urban League Presents: Let's Get Rid of Rats, 1961; AV567 (Box 14, Reel 567)
  - Urban League Presents: Untitled, 1961; AV568 (Box 14, Reel 568)
  - Urban League Presents: Can You Afford a Co-op Apartment?, Part 1, 1961 December 31; AV569; WNYU (Radio station: New York, N.Y.). (Box 14, Reel 569)
  - Urban League Presents: The Reluctant African, 1961; AV1399 (Box 36, Reel 1399)
  - Urban League Presents: A Rabbi Looks at Bigotry, 1959; AV1451 (Box 38, Reel 1451)
  - Urban League Presents: Racial Discrimination in Music, 1959; AV1452 (Box 38, Reel 1452)
  - Urban League Presents: A Renewal Program for Harlem, 1959; AV1453 (Box 38, Reel 1453)
  - Urban League Presents: The Role of Youth, 1959; AV1454 (Box 38, Reel 1454)
  - Urban League Presents, 1959; AV1455 (Box 38, Reel 1455)
  - Urban League Presents: The Metcalf-Baker Fair Housing Bill (Part 1), 1959; AV1456 (Box 38, Reel 1456)
  - Urban League Presents: The Metcalf-Baker Fair Housing Bill (Part 2), 1959; AV1457 (Box 38, Reel 1457)
  - Urban League Presents: A Priest Looks at Bigotry, 1959; AV1458 (Box 38, Reel 1458)
  - Urban League Presents: Progress for the Negro Worker, 1959; AV1459 (Box 38, Reel 1459)
  - Urban League Presents: A Psychiatrist Looks at Bigotry (Part 1), 1959; AV1460 (Box 38, Reel 1460)
  - The Irish Muse: An Evening of Readings New York University Producer: Elisa Guarino, 1993 April 27; AV1679; Guarino, Elisa (Box 44, Cassette 1679)
    Technical Requirements
    Original format: VHS
  - Community councils--informational, 1981 May 5; AV1850 (Box 48, Item 1850)
    Source of acquisition
    David Gail
  - Taking the Right Steps: A Guide to Career Planning and Placement (master), 1987; AV1851 (Box 48, Item 1851)
  - Elmer Holmes Bobst memorial service (tape 1 of 2), undated; AV1852 (Box 48, Item 1852)
  - Elmer Holmes Bobst memorial service (tape 2 of 2), undated; AV1853 (Box 48, Item 1853)
  - Elmer Holmes Bobst memorial service (tape 1 of 2, backup), undated; AV1854 (Box 48, Item 1854)
  - Elmer Holmes Bobst memorial service (tape 2 of 2, backup), undated; AV1855 (Box 48, Item 1855)
  - Conversation with Harold Hudson Channer (Group W Cable Vision Systems), 1983 August 24; AV1856 (Box 48, Item 1856)
    Scope and contents
    Frank Ferrell may also appear on this video. Originally broadcast by the Manhattan and Group W Cable Vison systems in New York City Wednesday, August 24, 1983, at 11:00 pm.
    Brademas, John, 1927-
  - Cutbacks in student aid (WCBS-TV news), undated; AV1857 (Box 48, Item 1857)
  - Straight Talk (WOR TV), 1985 October 2; AV1858 (Box 48, Item 1858)
  - Lecture: Moshe Dayan (Great Speakers Series) (tape 1 of 3), 1974 November 4; AV1859; Dayan, Moshe, 1915-1981 (Box 48, Item 1859)
    Physical characteristics and technical requirements
    Filmed in black and white. Recorded in mono.
  - Lecture: Moshe Dayan (Great Speakers Series) (tape 3 of 3), 1974 November 4; AV1861; Dayan, Moshe, 1915-1981 (Box 49, Item 1861)
  - Lebost space age windmill/wind turbine (edited), undated; AV1862 (Box 49, Item 1862)
    This tape may depict a windmill atop the Barney Building.
  - First Huntley Memorial Award presentation (tape 2 of ?), undated; AV1865 (Box 49, Item 1865)
    Original format: 3/4" Umatic
    Related materials
    This tape is related to RG 46.8, Records of the Presentation of University Awards.
  - Second Huntley Memorial Award presentation (tape 1 of 2), undated; AV1866 (Box 49, Item 1866)
    Original format: 3/4" Umatic. Recorded in mono.
  - Second Huntley Memorial Award presentation (tape 2 of 2), undated; AV1867 (Box 49, Item 1867)
  - Lecture: Moshe Dayan (Great Speakers Series) (tape 2 of 3), 1974 November 4; AV1860; Dayan, Moshe, 1915-1981 (Box 48, Item 1860)
  - Ireland House Dedication (Original), 26 April 1993; AV1968 (Box 50, Cassette 1968)
    Technical requirements
    Original format: audio cassette, SA90, TDK This is the master version of this recording.
    This cassette is related to materials transferred to the University Archives by Campus Media Support Services, acc. 93-019, and to other materials in RG 46.4.
    Barcode
    3 1142 04655057 3